<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss" 
	>
<channel>
	<title>
	Comments on: The ups and the downs continue	</title>
	<atom:link href="/blog/2011/05/07/the-ups-and-the-downs-continue/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/blog/2011/05/07/the-ups-and-the-downs-continue/</link>
	<description>my little place on the web</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 05:57:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>
		By: Sharon Cohen		</title>
		<link>/blog/2011/05/07/the-ups-and-the-downs-continue/#comment-10</link>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Sharon Cohen]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2011 13:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/travel/the-ups-and-the-downs-continue/#comment-10</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[You doing so much fun 
I wish I could do all of this...
Thanks man!
-Sharon]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You doing so much fun<br />
I wish I could do all of this&#8230;<br />
Thanks man!<br />
-Sharon</p>
]]></content:encoded>
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>
		By: Stefan		</title>
		<link>/blog/2011/05/07/the-ups-and-the-downs-continue/#comment-5</link>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Stefan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2011 16:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/travel/the-ups-and-the-downs-continue/#comment-5</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In reply to &lt;a href=&quot;/blog/2011/05/07/the-ups-and-the-downs-continue/#comment-4&quot;&gt;John&lt;/a&gt;.

Hi John,

My RTW packing list has been quite good so far as there isn&#039;t anything that I&#039;ve immediately needed / missed, but there are a couple of things that I could have brought along - altitude pills, a lonely planet guide book (not the Footprint one I had), vaseline (sunburnt lips), sleeping shorts rather than relying on boxers... Its sundries mainly which I&#039;ve been able to pick up here quite easily. The only thing I wished I had, but couldn&#039;t find - decent quick drying socks. Nights here are cold and it&#039;s nigh on impossible to dry clothes, that includes the quick-drying boxers and towel! 

In terms of essentials, a familiar alarm clock (you have to wake at 5am so need to know you can wake), my spare camera battery (wish I&#039;d brought 2 spares) and jeans! Jeans are big, bulky, heavy, terrible in the wet but they make you feel &quot;normal&quot; amongst the travel clothes wearing holiday makers. On that subject, I do wish I&#039;d brought a some &quot;normal&quot; clothes though - I went with the cargo shorts &#038; shirts as they are more verstatile for me and more usable on treks, but it does make you stand out a little in towns. You can tell the holiday makers as they are all wearing these sorts of clothes and someone asked if I worked at Machu Picchu yesterday as I &quot;had a uniform&quot;. Still, clothes are cheap enough here so I&#039;ll grab a couple of t-shirts and jobs a good-un :)

In terms of things I shouldn&#039;t have brought - the big notepad (I&#039;ve got a smaller one instead), the 30l rucksack (it&#039;s great for the Inca Trail and presumably buses, but it&#039;s usless to carry around).

I hope your travels go well! It&#039;s nerve-wracking, but there are some great people around and whilst it&#039;s tough, it&#039;s fun as well. I just need to get the ratio of fun up!

Stef]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In reply to <a href="/blog/2011/05/07/the-ups-and-the-downs-continue/#comment-4">John</a>.</p>
<p>Hi John,</p>
<p>My RTW packing list has been quite good so far as there isn&#8217;t anything that I&#8217;ve immediately needed / missed, but there are a couple of things that I could have brought along &#8211; altitude pills, a lonely planet guide book (not the Footprint one I had), vaseline (sunburnt lips), sleeping shorts rather than relying on boxers&#8230; Its sundries mainly which I&#8217;ve been able to pick up here quite easily. The only thing I wished I had, but couldn&#8217;t find &#8211; decent quick drying socks. Nights here are cold and it&#8217;s nigh on impossible to dry clothes, that includes the quick-drying boxers and towel! </p>
<p>In terms of essentials, a familiar alarm clock (you have to wake at 5am so need to know you can wake), my spare camera battery (wish I&#8217;d brought 2 spares) and jeans! Jeans are big, bulky, heavy, terrible in the wet but they make you feel &#8220;normal&#8221; amongst the travel clothes wearing holiday makers. On that subject, I do wish I&#8217;d brought a some &#8220;normal&#8221; clothes though &#8211; I went with the cargo shorts &amp; shirts as they are more verstatile for me and more usable on treks, but it does make you stand out a little in towns. You can tell the holiday makers as they are all wearing these sorts of clothes and someone asked if I worked at Machu Picchu yesterday as I &#8220;had a uniform&#8221;. Still, clothes are cheap enough here so I&#8217;ll grab a couple of t-shirts and jobs a good-un 🙂</p>
<p>In terms of things I shouldn&#8217;t have brought &#8211; the big notepad (I&#8217;ve got a smaller one instead), the 30l rucksack (it&#8217;s great for the Inca Trail and presumably buses, but it&#8217;s usless to carry around).</p>
<p>I hope your travels go well! It&#8217;s nerve-wracking, but there are some great people around and whilst it&#8217;s tough, it&#8217;s fun as well. I just need to get the ratio of fun up!</p>
<p>Stef</p>
]]></content:encoded>
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>
		By: John		</title>
		<link>/blog/2011/05/07/the-ups-and-the-downs-continue/#comment-4</link>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[John]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2011 15:11:46 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/travel/the-ups-and-the-downs-continue/#comment-4</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Hi Stefan,

I came across your site while researching what I would need to take for my own round the world trip that I am planning to start this year.. I see that you are about a week into your trip now.. any immediate thoughts about the stuff you&#039;ve taken - what is most essential, what you think you could have left behind, what you wish you had taken but didn&#039;t? It would be interesting to hear your opinion now, then again in a couple of months!

Hope you&#039;re doing well and experiencing many great things out there in world,

-John]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hi Stefan,</p>
<p>I came across your site while researching what I would need to take for my own round the world trip that I am planning to start this year.. I see that you are about a week into your trip now.. any immediate thoughts about the stuff you&#8217;ve taken &#8211; what is most essential, what you think you could have left behind, what you wish you had taken but didn&#8217;t? It would be interesting to hear your opinion now, then again in a couple of months!</p>
<p>Hope you&#8217;re doing well and experiencing many great things out there in world,</p>
<p>-John</p>
]]></content:encoded>
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
