<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss" 
	>
<channel>
	<title>
	Comments on: The Inca Trail and Machu Picchu	</title>
	<atom:link href="/blog/2011/05/13/the-inca-trail-and-machu-picchu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/blog/2011/05/13/the-inca-trail-and-machu-picchu/</link>
	<description>my little place on the web</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 05:57:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>
		By: Stefan		</title>
		<link>/blog/2011/05/13/the-inca-trail-and-machu-picchu/#comment-7</link>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Stefan]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2011 18:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=291#comment-7</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In reply to &lt;a href=&quot;/blog/2011/05/13/the-inca-trail-and-machu-picchu/#comment-6&quot;&gt;30 White Llamas&lt;/a&gt;.

If you arrive to Cusco early enough then you should be ok - the trick is to take things very easy and appreciate that you will probably feel poorly (a little sick, headaches, dizzyness etc). The walk itself isn&#039;t that hard, it&#039;s all about mental attitude and just pushing through the difficulties and the impossibility to breathe! I was drinking coca tea in the morning but didn&#039;t chew on coca leaves - for me it wasn&#039;t that bad enough. I had altitude pills too, but they were making me feel worse!

There are cold showers, but to be honest, you wouldn&#039;t want to use them (they are filthy) - I just stripped to the waste and washed in the sinks. At the last campsite there are hot showers, but by then I had no clean clothes - what is the point of a getting clean to pu on dirty clothes!

Aguas Calientes is very much a tourist town - lots of pizza places, noise... Don&#039;t expect it to be brilliant. It is also very expensive (a pizza was S/31, compared to Cusco at S/15). A couple that were on our tour had two nights booked in the town but were aiming to leave the next day after they saw the town.

Good luck on your trek, it&#039;s lots of fun!

Stef]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In reply to <a href="/blog/2011/05/13/the-inca-trail-and-machu-picchu/#comment-6">30 White Llamas</a>.</p>
<p>If you arrive to Cusco early enough then you should be ok &#8211; the trick is to take things very easy and appreciate that you will probably feel poorly (a little sick, headaches, dizzyness etc). The walk itself isn&#8217;t that hard, it&#8217;s all about mental attitude and just pushing through the difficulties and the impossibility to breathe! I was drinking coca tea in the morning but didn&#8217;t chew on coca leaves &#8211; for me it wasn&#8217;t that bad enough. I had altitude pills too, but they were making me feel worse!</p>
<p>There are cold showers, but to be honest, you wouldn&#8217;t want to use them (they are filthy) &#8211; I just stripped to the waste and washed in the sinks. At the last campsite there are hot showers, but by then I had no clean clothes &#8211; what is the point of a getting clean to pu on dirty clothes!</p>
<p>Aguas Calientes is very much a tourist town &#8211; lots of pizza places, noise&#8230; Don&#8217;t expect it to be brilliant. It is also very expensive (a pizza was S/31, compared to Cusco at S/15). A couple that were on our tour had two nights booked in the town but were aiming to leave the next day after they saw the town.</p>
<p>Good luck on your trek, it&#8217;s lots of fun!</p>
<p>Stef</p>
]]></content:encoded>
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>
		By: 30 White Llamas		</title>
		<link>/blog/2011/05/13/the-inca-trail-and-machu-picchu/#comment-6</link>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[30 White Llamas]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2011 16:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=291#comment-6</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[What an awesome run-down of the experience! I really enjoyed reading this, and I&#039;m now excited (and a little anxious - the altitude is a worry for me - did you chew coca leaves or anything?) about when I get to go! I am so curious - did you all carry your wine &#038; beer up the trek? When you talk of washing off, were there streams/showers/water nearby, or did you use the camping-type wet wipes? I&#039;m also staying in Aguas Calientes for a night, so kudos for the tips on the springs!
I&#039;m so happy to hear about your trek, and I am so glad you said hi on Twitter - thanks for posting this, and thanks for sharing part of your incredible journey!]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What an awesome run-down of the experience! I really enjoyed reading this, and I&#8217;m now excited (and a little anxious &#8211; the altitude is a worry for me &#8211; did you chew coca leaves or anything?) about when I get to go! I am so curious &#8211; did you all carry your wine &amp; beer up the trek? When you talk of washing off, were there streams/showers/water nearby, or did you use the camping-type wet wipes? I&#8217;m also staying in Aguas Calientes for a night, so kudos for the tips on the springs!<br />
I&#8217;m so happy to hear about your trek, and I am so glad you said hi on Twitter &#8211; thanks for posting this, and thanks for sharing part of your incredible journey!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
